And over here, I come and just try to start a conversation with it.
So it also has a record audio option.
I don't even know what it is.
It's a little bit weird, but let me click on it.
It will probably about dictation.
So it will probably convert what I say.
Stop recording to a text, right?
Yes, exactly, right?
So, yep, let's use this option and ask hyperwrite to introduce it to us.
Because I think he or she is the best one to do that, right?
So I click on a record audio, hello, hyperwrite.
I am a new user of you.
And what I want to know about you is that how do you function?
And what are the main differences that you have with other tools like chat GPT, etc.
And what do you do?
How can I use you?
What are the most used and what are the best use cases of this very tool called hyperwrite?
And by clicking stop recording, I will be able to wait a little bit and get what I just said in the text format.